Guide to the United Automobile Workers of America, District 65 Records WAG 006
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VII: Shop Files, 1937-1971 (Box 68 - 154)
  - O-PA
    - Omar Inc, 1944-1954 (Box 121, Folder 6-8)
    - Orthodontists Service, 1956-1958 (Box 121, Folder 9)
    - Oxford Handkerchief, 1942-1949 (Box 121, Folder 10-11)
    - P.S. Creations Inc, 1954-1966 (Box 121, Folder 12)
    - Palm Shore Dry Goods, 1941-1965 (Box 121, Folder 13)
    - Palumbo Cigar Co, 1947-1948 (Box 121, Folder 14)
    - Paramount Container, 1946-1954 (Box 121, Folder 15)
    - Park Drug Co (see Box 122), 1949-1958 (Box 121, Folder 16-17)
  - PA-PE
    - Park Drug Co (includes material on CIO #121) (see Box 121), 1948-1958 (Box 122, Folder 1)
    - Parles Fox Corp, 1950-1963 (Box 122, Folder 2-3)
    - M.W. Parsons--Plymouth Inc, 1959-1963 (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - Pavillon Fabric, 1957-1961 (Box 122, Folder 5)
    - Pauker Bros, 1947-1952 (Box 122, Folder 6)
    - Pecheur Lozenges, 1949-1954 (Box 122, Folder 7-9)
    - Peerless Sample Card, 1941-1960 (Box 122, Folder 10-14)
    - Pen & Brush Studios, 1941-1950 (Box 122, Folder 15)
    - J. C. Penney, 1946-1947 (Box 122, Folder 16)
  - PE-PO
    - Penthouse Manufacturing, 1960-1965 (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - Peter Puppet Playthings, Inc., 1949-1961 (Box 123, Folder 2-3)
    - Perfect Letter, 1945-1957 (Box 123, Folder 4)
    - Perfo Mat, 1956-1963 (Box 123, Folder 5-6)
    - A.M. Perlman, 1941-1957 (Box 123, Folder 7-8)
    - Perma Plating, 1957-1958 (Box 123, Folder 9)
    - Phi Betta Kappa, 1946-1952 (Box 123, Folder 10)
    - Plastic Heatsealers, 1953-1959 (Box 123, Folder 11-12)
    - Plymouth Corrugated, 1942-1949 (Box 123, Folder 13)
    - Polak & Schwarz, 1941-1949 (Box 123, Folder 14)
    - Polarad Electronics, 1951 (Box 123, Folder 15)
    - Charles Polk, 1943-1960 (Box 123, Folder 16)
    - Leo Pollack, 1949 (Box 123, Folder 17)
    - H. Pomerantz, 1940-1961 (Box 123, Folder 18)
    - W. S. Ponton (includes UOPWA #14 and AFL raid), 1950-1951 (Box 123, Folder 19)
  - PO-Q
    - I. Posner, Inc.(includes AFL raid), 1959-1965 (Box 124, Folder 1-2)
    - Posner Distributing and Posner Beauty and Barber Supply (includes strike), 1952-1963 (Box 124, Folder 3-4)
    - Prentice Hall, 1960-1962 (Box 124, Folder 5)
    - Premier Metal Products, 1952-1954 (Box 124, Folder 6)
    - Premier Manufacturing, 1963-1965 (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - Progressive Party (UOPWA Local 16), 1946-1947 (Box 124, Folder 8)
    - Progressive Quilting, 1943-1957 (Box 124, Folder 9)
    - Providence New York Findings, 1957 (Box 124, Folder 10)
    - Prudential Dental Lab (Local 201 UOPWA Dental Technicians), 1946-1961 (Box 124, Folder 11-12)
    - Public Affairs Committee (raid on UOPWA by AFL), 1946-1962 (Box 124, Folder 13-15)
    - Public Notion, 1953-1964 (Box 124, Folder 16)
    - Pur-All Paint Products, 1947-1949 (Box 124, Folder 17)
    - Purepac (raid by AFL), 1943-1948 (Box 124, Folder 18-19)
    - Pyramid Industrial Finishing, 1963-1969 (Box 124, Folder 20)
    - Q & R Dry Goods, 1941-1954 (Box 124, Folder 21)
    - Quality Dental Laboratories, 1955-1960 (Box 124, Folder 22-23)
  - R-RA
    - RCH Letter, 1959 (Box 125, Folder 1)
    - R.L. Polk, 1945-1962 (Box 125, Folder 2-3)
    - Rainbow, 1948-1949 (Box 125, Folder 4)
    - Rand Tea and Coffee, 1942-1950 (Box 125, Folder 5-7)
    - Random House (UOPWA), 1945-1951 (Box 125, Folder 8-11)
    - Rapid Mail, 1960-1962 (Box 125, Folder 12-15)
    - Rashkind Textile, 1950-1963 (Box 125, Folder 16)
    - Rayget Woolen, 1956-1965 (Box 125, Folder 17)
    - Raymond Services (see Box 126), 1946-1961 (Box 125, Folder 18-29)
  - RA-RE
    - Raymond Services (see Box 125), 1950-1954 (Box 126, Folder 1-2)
    - Red Seal Foot Fashion (Local 121, United Chemical Workers including strike), 1947-1954 (Box 126, Folder 3)
    - Rediker Brothers, 1956-1961 (Box 126, Folder 4)
    - Regal Knitwear, 1938-1943 (Box 126, Folder 5)
    - Regatta Knitwear, 1962-1963 (Box 126, Folder 6)
    - Rego Letter Service, 1960-1967 (Box 126, Folder 7)
    - Reiss Brothers, 1951-1954 (Box 126, Folder 8)
    - Reliable Quilting, 1952-1953 (Box 126, Folder 9)
    - Reliance Wool & Quilting(IBT Local 875), 1954-1956 (Box 126, Folder 10)
    - Renewal Mfg., 1947-1948 (Box 126, Folder 11)
    - Rennert, 1951 (Box 126, Folder 12)
    - Renoir Fabrics, 1940-1949 (Box 126, Folder 13)
    - Republic Container-Corrugated, 1950-1961 (Box 126, Folder 14-17)
    - Revlon (see Box 127), 1950-1955 (Box 126, Folder 18-19)
  - RE-RO
    - Revlon (see Box 126), 1942-1955 (Box 127, Folder 1-8)
    - Rialto Service Bureau, 1960-1961 (Box 127, Folder 9)
    - Ribbon Craft, 1963 (Box 127, Folder 10)
    - J. Richman, 1939-1960 (Box 127, Folder 11)
    - Ritz Foods, 1946-1947 (Box 127, Folder 12)
    - Riverdale Children's Association (SSEU #19, UOPWA), 1949-1951 (Box 127, Folder 13)
    - Roberts Foods (Local 124), 1949-1951 (Box 127, Folder 14)
    - Rokeach Foods (including strike and move to N.J.), 1946-1954 (Box 127, Folder 15-17)
    - Rainbow Container & Quality Box, 1941-1955 (Box 127, Folder 18)
    - Rollash (see Box 128), 1958-1961 (Box 127, Folder 19)
  - RO
    - Rollash (see Box 127), 1958-1962 (Box 128, Folder 1-3)
    - Rollon Rubber, 1948-1957 (Box 128, Folder 4-5)
    - Ro-Nat, 1959-1967 (Box 128, Folder 6)
    - Ronar, 1960 (Box 128, Folder 7)
    - William Rose, 1941-1949 (Box 128, Folder 8)
    - I. Rosenberg Cut Edge Ribbon-Processing (including strike), 1952-1958 (Box 128, Folder 9-10)
    - Rosenbluth Brothers, 1936-1966 (Box 128, Folder 11-13)
    - J. Rosenholz, 1938-1948 (Box 128, Folder 14)
    - J. Rosenthal-Jayar, 1942-1957 (Box 128, Folder 15)
    - Philip Rosenthal, 1949-1952 (Box 128, Folder 16)
    - Rosewood Fabrics (jurisdictional dispute with Textile Workers Local 1733), 1953-1956 (Box 128, Folder 17)
    - Rosko Textile, 1952-1954 (Box 128, Folder 18)
    - Leon Rothenberg Textile, 1956-1961 (Box 128, Folder 19-20)
    - Morris Rothkopf, 1941-1957 (Box 128, Folder 21)
    - S. Rothkopf (see Box 129), 1941-1957 (Box 128, Folder 22-23)
  - RO-SA
    - S. Rothkopf (see Box 128), 1941-1967 (Box 129, Folder 1-2)
    - Philip Rothman (lockout), 1939-1948 (Box 129, Folder 3)
    - Roto Lith, 1949 (Box 129, Folder 4)
    - Roure Dupont (CGT), 1947-1950 (Box 129, Folder 5)
    - Royal Lumber, 1949-1954 (Box 129, Folder 6)
    - Royal Office Supply, 1949-1953 (Box 129, Folder 7)
    - Royaloy, 1959-1960 (Box 129, Folder 8)
    - Royal Ribbon Mills (includes Textile Workers, CIO #1818), 1953-1954 (Box 129, Folder 9)
    - Royal Sewing Machine, 1950 (Box 129, Folder 10)
    - Rubber Waste, 1941-1948 (Box 129, Folder 11-13)
    - Rubin Textile, 1950-1955 (Box 129, Folder 14)
    - Rundback Chapman, 1947-1954 (Box 129, Folder 15)
    - Rutger Fabrics, 1942-1957 (Box 129, Folder 16-17)
    - S N News, n.d. (Box 129, Folder 18)
    - S.N.A. Stationery, 1942-1949 (Box 129, Folder 19)
    - S.T. Palay Textile, 1960 (Box 129, Folder 20)
    - Sample Card Board of Trade, 1943-1963 (Box 129, Folder 21-22)
    - Monroe Sanders (see Box 130), 1953-1965 (Box 129, Folder 23-24)
  - SA-SCH
    - Monroe Sanders (see Box 129), 1947-1966 (Box 130, Folder 1-4)
    - Sandoz Chemical, 1948-1950 (Box 130, Folder 5-6)
    - Sanita Paper Products, 1959 (Box 130, Folder 7)
    - Sanitary Supply, 1949-1957 (Box 130, Folder 8)
    - Saturday Review Associates (UOPWA), 1946-1949 (Box 130, Folder 9)
    - Saxon Plastics, 1954-1965 (Box 130, Folder 10)
    - Albert E. Schimmez, 1960-1965 (Box 130, Folder 11)
    - Arthur Schottenfeld, 1956-1963 (Box 130, Folder 12)
    - Schranz & Bieber (strike)(see Box 131), 1950-1963 (Box 130, Folder 13-15)
  - SCH
    - Schranz & Bieber (see Box 130), 1946-1963 (Box 131, Folder 1-6)
    - Schwab Rubber (strike), 1947-1960 (Box 131, Folder 7-11)
    - Schwartz Brothers Fabrics, 1949-1952 (Box 131, Folder 12)
    - Schwartz & Gilbert, 1937-1949 (Box 131, Folder 13-14)
    - Schwartz-Liebman Textile, 1963 (Box 131, Folder 15)
    - A. Schwartz-Zuckerman, 1941-1960 (Box 131, Folder 16)
    - FAO Schwartz, 1949 (Box 131, Folder 17)
    - H & S Schwartz, 1949-1962 (Box 131, Folder 18)
  - SCH-SHE
    - Max Schwartz, 1946-1947 (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - Scientic American, 1948-1951 (Box 132, Folder 2)
    - Screen Tek (strike), 1949-1951 (Box 132, Folder 3)
    - Security Mills, 1958-1959 (Box 132, Folder 4)
    - Security Packing, 1949-1952 (Box 132, Folder 5)
    - Lov Seidman, 1949-1968 (Box 132, Folder 6)
    - Seligman & Latz, 1950 (Box 132, Folder 7)
    - Seneca Quilting, 1947-1963 (Box 132, Folder 8)
    - Sepe Discount Store, 1962 (Box 132, Folder 9)
    - Service Backing, 1949-1950 (Box 132, Folder 10)
    - Service Corrugated, 1953 (Box 132, Folder 11)
    - Service Quilting, 1942-1948 (Box 132, Folder 12)
    - Settineri's (strike, Local 303), 1949-1950 (Box 132, Folder 13)
    - Louis Shamen, 1952-1966 (Box 132, Folder 14)
    - Shane & Hays, 1941-1956 (Box 132, Folder 15)
    - Shapiro Jobbing, 1947-1962 (Box 132, Folder 16)
    - Louis R. Shapiro, 1949 (Box 132, Folder 17)
    - Shelby Fabrics, 1962-1963 (Box 132, Folder 18)
    - Sheltering Arms Children's Service (UOPWA Local l9), 1948-1950 (Box 132, Folder 19)
    - Shelton Corrugated, 1950-1955 (Box 132, Folder 20-21)
  - SHE-SL
    - Shelton Manufacturing, 1940-1960 (Box 133, Folder 1-4)
    - Shepher, 1953 (Box 133, Folder 5)
    - Shepherd Knitwear, 1942-1959 (Box 133, Folder 6-8)
    - Sheraton Mills, 1952 (Box 133, Folder 9)
    - Sheridan Creations, 1960 (Box 133, Folder 10)
    - Sher-Win (Swiss American Watch), 1948-1952 (Box 133, Folder 11)
    - M. Shiller (Local 830), 1947-1948 (Box 133, Folder 12)
    - Shoe Wholesalers (strike), 1941-1943 (Box 133, Folder 13-14)
    - Silent Watchman, 1943-1949 (Box 133, Folder 15)
    - Robin Skall, 1952-1963 (Box 133, Folder 16-17)
    - Sklarin-Hammer, 1957-1958 (Box 133, Folder 18)
    - Slifka Fabrics, 1942-1963 (Box 133, Folder 19-21)
  - SO-ST
    - South Shore Drugs, 1943-1957 (Box 134, Folder 1-2)
    - Southerners Bargain House, 1941-1948 (Box 134, Folder 3-4)
    - Spanbock & Schaefer, 1945-1953 (Box 134, Folder 5-6)
    - Spiegel Novelty, 1957 (Box 134, Folder 7)
    - Spiegel Brothers, 1946-1948 (Box 134, Folder 8)
    - Henry Spitzer, 1942-1961 (Box 134, Folder 9-10)
    - Sportmens Accessories (strike), 1950-1951 (Box 134, Folder 11)
    - Spuncraft, ca.1946 (Box 134, Folder 12)
    - Stallo Mfg., 1959 (Box 134, Folder 13)
    - Stamp & Stationery Service, 1941-1944 (Box 134, Folder 14)
    - Standard Beauty Supply, 1942-1958 (Box 134, Folder 15-16)
    - Standard Corrugated, 1945-1949 (Box 134, Folder 17)
    - Standard Factors, 1962-1964 (Box 134, Folder 18)
    - Standard Reference Works Publishing, 1957-1965 (Box 134, Folder 19-20)
    - Standard Sample, 1941-1950 (Box 134, Folder 21-22)
    - Standard Specialty Sales (see Box 135), 1944-1963 (Box 134, Folder 23)
  - ST
    - Standard Specialty Sales (see Box 134), 1943-1963 (Box 135, Folder 1)
    - State Dental Technicians (UOPWA #201), 1950-1952 (Box 135, Folder 2)
    - State Dental Labor, 1950-1956 (Box 135, Folder 3)
    - Sterling Movies, U.S.A., 1959 (Box 135, Folder 4-5)
    - Fisher-Stevens Service, 1950-1955 (Box 135, Folder 6)
    - J.K. Stiefel, 1943-1964 (Box 135, Folder 7-8)
    - Stonehill Lab (AFL raid), 1953-1956 (Box 135, Folder 9)
    - Strahs Aluminum, 1940-1949 (Box 135, Folder 10)
    - Strauss Stores (AFL raid)(see Box 136), 1949-1954 (Box 135, Folder 11-19)
  - ST-SU
    - Strauss Stores (strike, raid) (See Box 135), 1945-1953 (Box 136, Folder 1-3)
    - Strike File (picketing assignments, Midtown Division), 1945 (Box 136, Folder 4)
    - Carole Stupell (strike), 1947-1949 (Box 136, Folder 5)
    - Herman Sukon, 1948-1964 (Box 136, Folder 6-7)
    - Summers Textile (strike), 1949 (Box 136, Folder 8)
    - Sun Radio & Electronics, 1949-1963 (Box 136, Folder 9-10)
    - Superior Television, 1949-1950 (Box 136, Folder 11)
    - Super-Vision Television, 1949-1950 (Box 136, Folder 12)
    - Supreme Fabrics, 1945-1962 (Box 136, Folder 13)
    - Supreme Refoldering, 1958-1962 (Box 136, Folder 14)
    - Supreme Textile, 1941-1951 (Box 136, Folder 15)
    - Suspender & Garter Manufacturers Association, 1942-1962 (Box 136, Folder 16-18)
  - T-TRI
    - Title Guarantee & Trust (UOPWA), 1942-1948 (Box 137, Folder 1-3)
    - Tally Ho, 1941-1959 (Box 137, Folder 4-5)
    - Television Maintenance (IBEW Local 3), 1949 (Box 137, Folder 6)
    - Times Square Hardware, 1951-1952 (Box 137, Folder 7)
    - Times Square Stores, 1948-1948 (Box 137, Folder 8-10)
    - Topps Hosiery (strike), 1942-1947 (Box 137, Folder 11)
    - Toy & Gift (N.Y. Merchandise) (strike), 1956-1959 (Box 137, Folder 12)
    - Transcontinental Machine Tool, 1955-1961 (Box 137, Folder 13-15)
    - TriCamp (strike), 1942-1949 (Box 137, Folder 16)
  - TRU-UNI
    - True Sullivan (UOPWA), 1950-1952 (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - True-Sullivan-Neibert (UOPWA), 1946-1949 (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - J. Turestsky, 1941-1952 (Box 138, Folder 3)
    - United Jewish Appeal (UOPWA), 1949 (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - Underwriters Salvage, 1945-1947 (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - Unicorn Press, 1941-1953 (Box 138, Folder 6-8)
    - Union News (strike), 1946-1960 (Box 138, Folder 9-13)
    - Union Novelty Shop, 1959-1960 (Box 138, Folder 14)
    - United Contact Lens, 1957-1963 (Box 138, Folder 15-16)
    - United Export, 1946-1950 (Box 138, Folder 17)
    - United Mailing, 1947-1954 (Box 138, Folder 18)
  - UNI-VA
    - United Service for New Americans, 1946-1950 (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - United Telephone Service (detailed notes on office procedures), ca.1952 (Box 139, Folder 2)
    - United Quilters, 1940-1954 (Box 139, Folder 3)
    - United Whelan (sex segregation, war-time lockout), 1941-1945 (Box 139, Folder 4-7)
    - University Dental Lab, 1948-1960 (Box 139, Folder 8)
    - Universal Fabricators (United Service Employees #377), 1947-1953 (Box 139, Folder 9)
    - UNO Tools, 1950-1952 (Box 139, Folder 10)
    - Uris Sales (includes sexual harassment case), 1940-1953 (Box 139, Folder 11-15)
    - Valdez Cigar Store, 1947-1952 (Box 139, Folder 16)
    - Vantine's Inc. (includes sex segregation, Puerto Rican worker), 1950-1961 (Box 139, Folder 17-18)
  - VA-VI
    - Van Iderstine, 1948-1950 (Box 140, Folder 1)
    - Vanetta Velvet (lock-out), 1941-1962 (Box 140, Folder 2-3)
    - Vickford, 1966 (Box 140, Folder 4)
    - Victory Quilting, 1943-1948 (Box 140, Folder 5-6)
    - Video Television, 1948-1951 (Box 140, Folder 7)
    - Viking Press, 1946-1951 (Box 140, Folder 8-9)
    - Vim Electric (CIO Local 830; strike) (see Box 141), 1946-1948 (Box 140, Folder 10-15)
  - VI-WAR
    - Vim Electric (strikes), 1949-1960 (Box 141, Folder 1-7)
    - Vita Products (strike), 1952-1957 (Box 141, Folder 8)
    - Paul Vogel, 1948-1955 (Box 141, Folder 9)
    - Vogue Instruments, 1957-1962 (Box 141, Folder 10)
    - Volk Hats, 1940-1941 (Box 141, Folder 11)
    - Volume Direct Mail (OPEIU Local 153), 1960-1963 (Box 141, Folder 12-13)
    - Vox Productions, 1946-1953 (Box 141, Folder 14)
    - Wyse Wear Mfg., 1943-1963 (Box 141, Folder 15)
    - Walcott Wool, 1951-1954 (Box 141, Folder 16)
    - J.A.Want Organization (AFL raid), 1947-1951 (Box 141, Folder 17)
    - Warehouse Office Organizing Committee (Woolworth), 1946-1947 (Box 141, Folder 18)
  - WAS-WE
    - Washburn & Harris, 1962 (Box 142, Folder 1)
    - Joe Wasserman (sex segregation), 1948-1964 (Box 142, Folder 2-3)
    - Wearever Shoe (Selburn Shoe), 1949-1962 (Box 142, Folder 4)
    - Wearite Gloves, 1941 (Box 142, Folder 5)
    - Wearwell Knitwear, 1940-1952 (Box 142, Folder 6)
    - Weil Ceramics, 1943-1965 (Box 142, Folder 7)
    - Louis Weinberg Associates, 1939-1942 (Box 142, Folder 8)
    - Daniel Weiner, 1941-1943 (Box 142, Folder 9)
    - J. Weiss Shoe, 1942-1955 (Box 142, Folder 10)
    - Welfare Council (UOPWA #19), 1947-1950 (Box 142, Folder 11)
    - Wellmade Suspender, 1941-1950 (Box 142, Folder 12)
    - Wender & Cohen, 1941-1957 (Box 142, Folder 13-14)
    - Wertex, 1949-1954 (Box 142, Folder 15)
    - Wertheimer (strike), 1950-1951 (Box 142, Folder 16-21)
    - Westchester Jewish Community Service (UOPWA #19), 1948-1951 (Box 142, Folder 22)
  - WH-WI
    - Whitlock (RCIA Local 1140), 1946-1968 (Box 143, Folder 1-7)
    - Widder Brothers, 1950-1960 (Box 143, Folder 8)
    - Wilgo (UOPWA), 1948-1958 (Box 143, Folder 9-10)
    - W.C. Williams, 1948-1952 (Box 143, Folder 11)
    - Williamsburg Lumber, 1943-1952 (Box 143, Folder 12)
    - Williamsburg Publishing, 1946-1960 (Box 143, Folder 13)
    - Wilness Mfg., 1954-1963 (Box 143, Folder 14-16)
    - W.S. Wilson (see Box 144), 1945-1950 (Box 143, Folder 17)
  - WI-WO
    - W.S. Wilson (see Box 143), 1946-1949 (Box 144, Folder 1)
    - Windsor Fabrics, 1943-1968 (Box 144, Folder 2)
    - Winston Electronics (IBEW 1430), 1950 (Box 144, Folder 3)
    - Winston Radio & Television (strike, IBEW 1430), 1949-1957 (Box 144, Folder 4)
    - Winthrop Mfg., 1956-1961 (Box 144, Folder 5)
    - Wintro Products, 1953-1956 (Box 144, Folder 6)
    - Wisconsin Farms, 1948-1951 (Box 144, Folder 7-10)
    - Wise Shoe, 1941-1960 (Box 144, Folder 11-12)
    - Charles Wolton, 1940-1964 (Box 144, Folder 13-14)
    - Womrath Books (UOPWA), 1946-1948 (Box 144, Folder 15)
    - Woolen Jobbers (war-time wildcat strikes)(see Box 145), 1939-1949 (Box 144, Folder 16-20)
  - WO-YA
    - Woolen Jobbers (Taft-Hartley), 1946-1952 (Box 145, Folder 1-3)
    - F.W. Woolworth (strikes, AFL #804, sex segregated wages), 1945-1948 (Box 145, Folder 4-8)
    - World Tourists (Taft-Hartley, Wallace campaign), 1945-1950 (Box 145, Folder 9)
    - Worth Hardware, 1946-1961 (Box 145, Folder 10-12)
    - Wrought Iron (ILA #1827), 1958-1959 (Box 145, Folder 13)
    - Wulcrest Knitwear, 1946-1948 (Box 145, Folder 14)
    - Rudolph Wurlitzer (Local 830), 1942-1948 (Box 145, Folder 15-16)
    - Yale Fabrics (strike), 1939-1949 (Box 145, Folder 17)
  - YA-Z
    - Yarnell Textile (Levine & Yagolnitzer), 1943-1958 (Box 146, Folder 1)
    - Young People's Records (UOPWA, lockout), 1950-1953 (Box 146, Folder 2)
    - Your Guide Publications, 1949-1953 (Box 146, Folder 3)
    - Z.K. Equipment, 1942-1950 (Box 146, Folder 4-5)
    - Zadek-Feldstein (women workers), 1946-1950 (Box 146, Folder 6-7)
    - Zimmerman's (UOPWA, OPEIU #153), 1941-1950 (Box 146, Folder 8)
    - Zip-A-Bag (discrimination against Jews), 1942-1948 (Box 146, Folder 9-10)
    - M. Zwaifler, 1939-1955 (Box 146, Folder 11)
    - Zy-Lite Optical, 1941-1963 (Box 146, Folder 12-15)
  - A-DEL
    - Acme Window Display, 1941-1950 (Box 147, Folder 1)
    - Agress Seed & Nut Co., 1953 (Box 147, Folder 2)
    - Alonzo Cigar Co., 1945-1957 (Box 147, Folder 3)
    - Amalgamated Lithographers Welfare Fund, 1948-1953 (Box 147, Folder 4)
    - American Pistachio, 1942 (Box 147, Folder 5)
    - Arlen Thread Co., 1954 (Box 147, Folder 6)
    - Art Jack Die Casting Inc., 1958-1959 (Box 147, Folder 7)
    - Associated Book Service, 1941 (Box 147, Folder 8)
    - Barth Binding, 1950 (Box 147, Folder 9)
    - A.S. Beck Shoe Corp., 1945 (Box 147, Folder 10)
    - Benson & Hedges, 1950-1951 (Box 147, Folder 11)
    - Berger Cigar Co., 1948-1960 (Box 147, Folder 12)
    - W.L. Blumberg Co., 1946 (Box 147, Folder 13)
    - H. Anton Bock, 1944-1954 (Box 147, Folder 14)
    - Breakstone, 1962-1968 (Box 147, Folder 15)
    - Broadway Fashions, 1948-1951 (Box 147, Folder 16-17)
    - C&L Restaurant, 1942-1950 (Box 147, Folder 18)
    - Sam Camitta, 1943-1946 (Box 147, Folder 19)
    - Canter China, 1947-1949 (Box 147, Folder 20)
    - Jose Capitano, 1946-1952 (Box 147, Folder 21)
    - Capital Publishing Co. & American Legal Publications Inc., 1948-1950 (Box 147, Folder 22)
    - Cello Masters, 1946-1951 (Box 147, Folder 23)
    - Childrens Service Bureau, 1948-1949 (Box 147, Folder 24)
    - Clareus Dental Lab., 1944-1954 (Box 147, Folder 25)
    - Clean-O-Chemical Co., 1949-1950 (Box 147, Folder 26)
    - J. Cohen Lumber Co., 1947-1949 (Box 147, Folder 27)
    - Comm. of Jewish Writers & Artists, 1946 (Box 147, Folder 28)
    - Concord Books Inc., 1947-1949 (Box 147, Folder 29)
    - Continental Hat Body Corp., 1941-1944 (Box 147, Folder 30)
    - L.T. Corbin, 1962 (Box 147, Folder 31)
    - Crest Fabrics, 1943-1949 (Box 147, Folder 32)
    - Dankowitz Cigar, 1946-1960 (Box 147, Folder 33)
    - Davega City Radio Inc., 1939 (Box 147, Folder 34)
    - Deluxe Mdse, 1937-1948 (Box 147, Folder 35)
  - DEN-GIB
    - De Nobili Cigar, 1946-1949 (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - Drug Merchandising, 1939-1954 (Box 148, Folder 2)
    - East Coast Millwork, 1946-1953 (Box 148, Folder 3)
    - Edbert Woodworking, 1946-1950 (Box 148, Folder 4)
    - Express Container, 1941, 1948 (Box 148, Folder 5)
    - El Felipe, 1945-1962 (Box 148, Folder 6)
    - Fibre Yarn Co., 1941-1949 (Box 148, Folder 7)
    - Fine Dental Lab., 1938, 1951 (Box 148, Folder 8)
    - H. Finkelstein & Sons, 1941-1948 (Box 148, Folder 9)
    - Frost Television, 1950 (Box 148, Folder 10)
    - Fulton Frame, 1942-1949 (Box 148, Folder 11-12)
    - Fur Health Fund, 1950-1951 (Box 148, Folder 13)
    - Seth Gaffen Shoes, 1946-1962 (Box 148, Folder 14)
    - Gage Bros. Inc., 1941-1947 (Box 148, Folder 15)
    - Garcia Saavedra Cigar Co., 1946-1956 (Box 148, Folder 16)
    - Garcia Suares, 1952-1960 (Box 148, Folder 17)
    - Garfield & Co., 1946-1947 (Box 148, Folder 18)
    - Garfield News, 1943-1950 (Box 148, Folder 19)
    - Garment Center #1 Exec. Board, 1963-1964 (Box 148, Folder 20)
    - Gaylord Container Corp., 1941-1944 (Box 148, Folder 21-25)
    - General Cigar Co., Inc., 1947-1948 (Box 148, Folder 26)
    - General Quilting Mfg. Co., 1941-1946 (Box 148, Folder 27)
    - George Cushing Textile, 1956-1958 (Box 148, Folder 28)
    - Gibralter Corrugated, 1940-1945 (Box 148, Folder 29)
  - GIB-HUD
    - Gibralter Corrugated, 1945 (Box 149, Folder 1)
    - S.J. Glick, 1940-1947 (Box 149, Folder 2)
    - Globe Shipping Co., Inc., 1947 (Box 149, Folder 3)
    - J. Goldberg Trimming Inc., 1941-1945 (Box 149, Folder 4)
    - Golding Bros. Co., 1940-1941 (Box 149, Folder 5-11)
    - A. Goldman, 1941-1943 (Box 149, Folder 12)
    - J.J. Goldstein, 1943-1944 (Box 149, Folder 13)
    - Victor Gonzales, 1946-1954 (Box 149, Folder 14)
    - Goodman & Sons, 1948 (Box 149, Folder 15)
    - Goodwear Knitwear Co., 1942-1948 (Box 149, Folder 16)
    - Grand Artificial Flower Corp., 1941 (Box 149, Folder 17)
    - Greater N.Y. Industrial Council, 1942-1947 (Box 149, Folder 18)
    - Eugene Green Inc., 1941 (Box 149, Folder 19)
    - Grin Textile Corp., 1945-1946 (Box 149, Folder 20)
    - Gurbob Co., 1946-1947 (Box 149, Folder 21)
    - Gustave Rubner, 1941-1942 (Box 149, Folder 22)
    - Guth Stern Co., 1941-1942 (Box 149, Folder 23)
    - Hahlo & Solomon, 1941 (Box 149, Folder 24)
    - Halperin Fab, 1942-1949 (Box 149, Folder 25)
    - Hammond Tole Co., 1948-1949 (Box 149, Folder 26)
    - Hardware Organizing Comm., 1943-1947 (Box 149, Folder 27-28)
    - Hardware Salesmen, 1946-1948 (Box 149, Folder 29)
    - Harlem-Adler & Co., Inc., 1954 (Box 149, Folder 30)
    - Harlem Book, 1946-1951 (Box 149, Folder 31)
    - Harlem Crockery, 1940-1946 (Box 149, Folder 32)
    - Harvard Mfg, 1939 (Box 149, Folder 33)
    - Hebrew Sheltering & Immigrant Society, 1948-1950 (Box 149, Folder 34)
    - Hedeman Products Inc., 1946-1947 (Box 149, Folder 35)
    - Hego Fabrics Inc., 1940-1943 (Box 149, Folder 36)
    - Helmar Mfg. Corp., 1957-1962 (Box 149, Folder 37)
    - Wm.E. Hinkel Co., 1946-1947 (Box 149, Folder 38)
    - D.L. Horowitz Inc., 1941-1943 (Box 149, Folder 39)
    - Houbigant, 1941-1946 (Box 149, Folder 40-41)
    - Howard Mfg. Co., 1941-1942 (Box 149, Folder 42)
    - Hudson Service & Storage, 1948-1956 (Box 149, Folder 43)
  - HY-KL
    - Hygrade Garter, 1941 (Box 150, Folder 1)